<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sudofy</string>
    <string name="splash_image">splash image</string>
    <string name="done">done</string>
    <string name="top_image">top image</string>

    <!--onBoard texts-->
    <string name="on_board3_text">Enjoy your responsibility!</string>
    <string name="on_board2_text">Rush to help with Sudofy</string>
    <string name="on_board1_text">A few clicks will get you there</string>

    <!--Description/Remedies-->
    <string name="desc_asphyxia"> asphyxia…</string>
    <string name="desc_epilepsy"> epilepsy…</string>
    <string name="desc_head_ache"> head ache… </string>
    <string name="desc_head_injury">Treat any suspected head injury with the utmost caution, as they have the
        potential to be very serious. Head injuries often lead to unconsciousness and all the attendant problems.
        Also, head injuries can cause permanent damage to the brain.\n\n<b>Introduction</b>\n\n Keep in mind that a
        casualty with any head injury may well be suffering from
        neck and spine injuries also.\nIf the casualty is or has been unconscious, you suspect a fractured skull, or
        their responses deteriorate CALL AN AMBULANCE IMMEDIATELY. Keep their airway clear and monitor their breathing.
        \n\n<b>Possible Treatments</b>\n\n

        <b>1.</b> If the casualty is unconscious, and you don’t wish to move them as you suspect
        neck injury, you can use the jaw thrust method of keeping the airway clear \n\n

        <b>2.</b> If you are unable to use the jaw thrust method, and you cannot keep the airway
        clear, put the casualty in the recovery position but make sure the head, neck and body are
        in line as you turn them to avoid any further damage to a neck or spinal injury. \n\n

        <b>3.</b>If the casualty is conscious, you can help them lie down, making sure to keep the
        head and neck in line with the body. You can help stop any movement of their head by placing
        your hands on either side of the head and keeping it still. \n\n

        <b>4.</b> If there is bleeding, help to control it by applying pressure directly to or around
        the wound. However, if there is blood or fluid coming from an ear, do not try to stop the flow,
        as the fluid must be allowed to drain. \n\n

        <b>Key points when treating head injuries</b>\n\n
        Monitor the casualty’s breathing, pulse and response
        levels. If the casualty appears to recover, monitor them closely as they may well deteriorate and their
        response levels drop.\n\n

        If a casualty has been concussed, try to make sure they are not left alone for the next 24 hours.
        Advise them to seek medical help as soon as possible.\n\n

        If a casualty suffers any of the following in the few days after concussion, they should go to
        A&amp;E immediately: worsening headache, nausea or vomiting, drowsiness, weakness in a limb, problems
        speaking, dizzy spells, blood or fluid from an ear or the nose, problems seeing, seizures or confusion.\n\n

        If the concussion is received playing sports, do not allow the concussed player to continue until they
        have seen a doctor. Usually, concussed players are not allowed to participate for up to three weeks after
        being concussed.\n\n Quick recovery!</string>

    <string name="desc_poisoning">poisoning…</string>
    <string name="desc_faint"> faint…</string>
    <string name="desc_burn"> burn…</string>
    <string name="desc_stroke"> stroke…</string>
    <string name="desc_drug_overdose"> drug overdose…</string>
    <string name="desc_heart_burn"> heart burn…</string>
    <string name="desc_fracture">fracture…</string>

</resources>